yes my mom can't answer the phone right now oh do you know when she'll be back this is the mental
health center and we wanted to follow up about making a counseling appointment
we don't need that kind of help
dianchen who was that dear uh it was spam
are you excited to finally meet dr chien
you're sure he's not a fraud
stop it dianchen you're scaring your sister i'll take care of her
i see you taught shishi some new science what did she say
she says i'm a good brother is that so i wonder why you teach her that the doctor is ready for you
yes we're coming
all right then what brings you in well it's my daughter about six months ago she suddenly
lost her voice we've seen all kinds of doctors but no answers yet
you're safe i'm here
you